

Katarzyna Pycińska

I am a student of computer science with a specialization in computer graphic at the Cracow University of Technology. I have experience in designing websites, web or mobile application. I am interested in photography and I have experience with Photoshop.

I would like to undertake an internship or work as UX/UI Designer or Frontend Developer.

Contact

Mobile: (+48) 512 186 010

Email: pycinskak@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/katarzy na-pycińska-87850a1a7/

Portfolio:

https://pycinskak.myportfolio.com

Work Experience

Junior Tools Developer Capgemini | June 2021 - Now

- Migration of mailboxes, solving incidents support via ServiceNow,
- Service automation Google Workspace, writing Scripts in AppScript that used Google Workspace (forms. sheets, mailbox, etc.)

Intern Tools Developer

Capgemini | December 2020 - June 2021

- SKI Jumping Applications for Polish National Ski Jumpers research and test new libraries, assist developers, learn the codebase and improve coding skills,
- Creating report in Excel on the basic of which the forecast is made,
- Application software testing, analysis and reporting of result.

Education

Cracow University of Technology 2021 - Now

Computer Science - Computer Graphic and Multimedia, master's degree

Cracow University of Technology

2021 - Now

Computer Science, engineer

Academic Experience

- "3P mobile application (storage, processing, transfer) for graphic content" engineering work written in Java and XML, using Android Studio, Firebase, Photoshop and Illustrator
- designing a graphical interface for a home help ordering application in Figma,
- designed a graphical interface for a web application courier company
- "Memory Game" a desktop application written in Java where game results are saved to the SQLite database with the use of a client-server connection,
- Website for an ophthalmology office written in JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Course

Basic photography Course, Academy Photography in Cracow

Technologies

Java, JavaFx, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Angular, XML, UML, SQL, PHP, Python, Git

Languages

English - fluent, Polish - native

Software

IntellJ IDEA, Android Studio, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Microsoft Suite, Google Workspace, Photoshop, Photoscape, iMovie, Illustrator, 3DSMax, Autocad, WordPress, SketchUp, Figma

Hobby

volleyball, photography, play musical instruments, design

Systems

Windows, MacOs, Android, iOS